Some people
break records in taking care of their own. The
record of giving a new car with their own savings and giving their mother a driving license. The
record of giving surprises to children of all ages. The record of breaking records of happiness and
establishing new ones. The record of
listening to old stories of dad in a new house. The record of
increasing laughter and establishing big ones. The record of not looking at the phone. The
record of breaking records of happiness and planning for every coming tomorrow.
Those who take care of their own not only keep them safe but
also keep them happy. For them,
ICICI Prudential Life has life
long plans. These
give life long happiness along with security. The record of happiness that they always
establish today and tomorrow.